asnews.com.sg 2018-08-31

# As Singapore

Nvia Gestión de Datos, SL and all related entities (the “Nvia Group") are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy explains:

  1. How we, through this website and any forms for submission of personal data on this website, use the information we collect about you;
  2. How you may instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information; and
  3. The procedures that we have to safeguard your privacy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy complements, and does not limit or replace, the purposes for which you provide us with your personal data which may be expressly stated in any form for submission of personal data to us through this website. 

Where this Privacy Policy conflicts with any other privacy policy or data protection policy of any member of our group of companies, this Privacy Policy will prevail in respect of data collected, used or disclosed by any member of the Nvia Group in Singapur.

## Information Collected

Visiting the website alone does not result in any personally identifiable data being collected or stored. The information that we collect and store during a visit to this website is meant to monitor use of this website and to help its further development. 

When you use certain pages of our website such as when you register to receive company announcements or fill in the contact form, we may ask you to provide personal information such as your name, email address, telephone number, and company. You will always know when we are collecting personal information, because we only do so when you voluntarily submit it to us through such online forms and/or e-mail.

We collect this information to provide you with any products or services that you may request or require, or to respond to your feedback or queries. If you send us an e-mail with questions or comments, we may use your personal information to respond to you, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. However, it is not our standard practice to send you any e-mail unless you request a particular service that involves e-mail communications. There may be times when you subscribe to an e-mail list that will send information about our company to your e-mail address.

We may share your personal information with members of the Nvia Group for administrative or operational purposes. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as permitted or required by the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (the “PDPA”) or any other law, including when we believe such disclosure to be necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with any court order, request from a regulator or any other legal process to which Nvia is subject.

## Access rights

In the event that you voluntarily submit to us any personal information, for us to collect and process, you have the right to access your personal data we held, to correct that personal data where it is inaccurate, incomplete, misleading or not up-to-date, and to withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal data. You may exercise these rights in writing by sending an e-mail to info@asnews.com.sg, attaching a scanned copy of your ID Card or Passport. 

## What Happens When I Link to Another Site?

This web site contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website. It should be noted that the websites made available via links may have different privacy policies and visitors are advised to read and understand the privacy statements of the respective website visit. 

## Amendment Policy 

In the event this Privacy Policy is revised, the amendments will be updated on this page. You will be updated with: the type of information that will be collected; how it is to be used and under what circumstances; and how information is to be shared with other parties.
